<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
<string name="about_text" tools:ignore="TypographyDashes,TypographyOther">
\nThe “Number Place Breaker” automatically solves Number Place puzzles, also known as Sudoku,
only by taking a picture of a puzzle.
It is not a practical application; Please consider it as an experiment or a proof-of-concept.
There is no guarantee this app works correctly.
Please use it on your own risk.
\n
\nFull source code of this program is available on Github at http://github.com/AlissaSabre/NumberPlace
\n
\nHOW TO USE THIS APP
\n
\n1. Touch [Capture] to start the camera.
\n
\n2. Take a picture of a Number Place puzzle by touching anywhere on the screen.
\n
\n3. Check the captured puzzle. There may be erros. You can correct them by touching the puzzle board.
\n
\n4. Touch [Solve] to let the app solve the puzzle and show the answer.
\n
\nNOTE ON OpenCV Manager
\n
\nThis app internally uses another app, “OpenCV Manager” for image processing.
It is available on Google Play for free.
The Number Place Breaker prompts you when it is needed.
Please install it if you want to use Capture function.
It can\'t capture a puzzle unless OpenCV Manager is installed.
\n
\nCREDITS
\n
\nNumber Place Breaker is written by Alissa Sabre (http://alissa-sabre.cocolog-nifty.com).
\n
\nThe solver part of this work was inspired by an excellent article by Naoyuki Tamura available as http://bach.istc.kobe-u.ac.jp/copris/puzzles/
\n
\nThis program may use and/or contain whole or parts of unmodified works from the following open source projects.
\n
\nOpen Source Computer Vision Library for Android (OpenCV4Android), version 2.4.6,
available through http://opencv.org 
as http://sourceforge.net/projects/opencvlibrary/files/opencv-android/2.4.6/OpenCV-2.4.6-android-sdk-r2.zip/download,
distributed under the following license:
\n
\n  IMPORTANT: READ BEFORE DOWNLOADING, COPYING, INSTALLING OR USING.
\n
\n   By downloading, copying, installing or using the software you agree to this license.
\n   If you do not agree to this license, do not download, install,
\n   copy or use the software.
\n
\n                            License Agreement
\n                 For Open Source Computer Vision Library
\n
\n  Copyright (C) 2000-2008, Intel Corporation, all rights reserved.
\n  Copyright (C) 2008-2011, Willow Garage Inc., all rights reserved.
\n  Third party copyrights are property of their respective owners.
\n
\n  Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
\n  are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
\n
\n    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
\n      this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
\n
\n    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
\n      this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
\n      and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
\n
\n    * The name of the copyright holders may not be used to endorse or promote products
\n      derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
\n
\n  This software is provided by the copyright holders and contributors "as is" and
\n  any express or implied warranties, including, but not limited to, the implied
\n  warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose are disclaimed.
\n  In no event shall the Intel Corporation or contributors be liable for any direct,
\n  indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages
\n  (including, but not limited to, procurement of substitute goods or services;
\n  loss of use, data, or profits; or business interruption) however caused
\n  and on any theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability,
\n  or tort (including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of
\n  the use of this software, even if advised of the possibility of such damage.
\n
\nSAT4J, version 2.3.4,
available on http://www.sat4j.org, distributed under a dual-license of
EPL 1.0 (http://www.eclipse.org/org/documents/epl-v10.php)
and LGPL 2.1 (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.en.html),
which is a derivative work of 
MiniSat, version 1.1.4 implementation, 
the source code for which can be found at www.minisat.se, 
under the following permissive license:
\n
\n  MiniSat -- Copyright (c) 2003-2005, Niklas Een, Niklas Sorensson
\n
\n  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a
\n  copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
\n  "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
\n  without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
\n  distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
\n  permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
\n  the following conditions:
\n
\n  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included
\n  in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
\n
\n  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS
\n  OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
\n  MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
\n  NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
\n  LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
\n  OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
\n  WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
\n
\n“数独” and/or “Sudoku” appear registered trademarks by NIKOLI Co., Ltd. in Japan and some other countries.
Other names of the same puzzle, e.g. “ナンプレ”, “ナンバープレース”, “Number Place” may be trademarks of someone in somewhere on this planet.
</string>
</resources>
